A Guide to the Mary Josephine King Papers, 1918-2003
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Mary Josephine King Papers, 1918-2003
The Library of Virginia
42309
18.55 cubic feet and 38 boxes
Mary Josephine King
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the estate of Mary Josephine King, Atlanta, Georgia. Video cd of Mary Josephine King interview on the Horton family gift of Harold Horton, Flowood, Mississippi.
Biographical Information
Mary Josephine King was born 29 April 1924 in Birmingham, Alabama, to John Berry King (1894-1934) and Susan Edith Smith King (1899-1981). Mary Jo King graduated from Central High School in Charlotte, North Carolina, in 1942, and from Presbyterian Hospital School of Nursing (Charlotte) in 1945. King taught nursing in Mississippi and in West Virginia, before accepting a position at Portsmouth (Virginia) General Hospital. After retiring from Portsmouth General, she taught part-time at Louise Obici School of Nursing. King was also a genealogist and belonged to several organizations. She did in-depth research on the King, Smith, and related families. Never married, Mary Josephine King died 22 October 2004 in Chesapeake, Virginia. She was buried in Forest Lawn Cemetery in Charlotte, North Carolina.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1918-2003, of Mary Josephine King (1924-2004) of Chesapeake, Virginia, and Charlotte, North Carolina, consisting of genealogical materials collected in doing research on the King, Smith, and related families, and includes genealogical notes and charts, correspondence, and photographs. Papers also include King's personal papers mainly concerning her education and career as a nursing instructor. The series is divided into five series: I: Family Genealogies; II: Genealogical Correspondence; III: Miscellaneous Genealogical Material; IV: Personal Papers; V: Oversize.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Family Genealogies
Genealogical Correspondence
Miscellaneous Genealogical Material
Personal Papers
Oversize
Contents List
- Series I: Family Genealogies., Extent: 24 boxes. (Box 1-24)
  Series I: Family Genealogies contains articles, Bible records, birth records, cemetery records, census records, clippings, correspondence, death records, deeds, genealogical notes and charts, judicial records, lists, maps, marriage records, military records, newsletters, notes, obituaries, photographs and negatives, scrapbooks, video cds, and wills concerning the Beachbord, Byrd, Calwell, Chamblee, Cockrell, Davis, Dodson, Eatman, Garvin, Gilbert, Goodson, Hansford, Horton (includes video cd of an interview with Mary Jo King concerning the family), King, Legg, Locker, McAfee, McDaniel, Peebles, Smith, Stamps, Tallent, Taylor, Walters, Williams, Winstead, and related families that settled in Virginia, Alabama, Arkansas, Georgia, Maryland, North Carolina, South Carolina, Tennessee, and Texas.
  alphabetical
  - Bailey Family. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Baker Family. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barnes Family. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Beachboard Family., folder 1 of 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Beachboard Family., folder 2 of 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Beachboard Family., folder 3 of 5 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beachboard Family., folder 4 of 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Beachboard Family., folder 5 of 5 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Beachboard Family. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Beachboard Family. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Beachboard Family. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Beachboard Family (Maryland). (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Beachboard Family (Tennessee). (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Benjamin Beachboard Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Benjamin Beachboard., folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Levi (Eli) Beachboard Family. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - William Beachboard Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - William Beachboard Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bernard Family. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bishop Family. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Black Family. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Black Family. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - James S. Black Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - James S. Black Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Robert Black, Sr., Family. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Robert Black, Jr., Family. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Byrd Family. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Calwell Family. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Campbell Family. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - George Stubblefield Campbell, Sr., Family. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Castleberry Family. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cawthon Family. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chamblee Family. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chamblee Family. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chamblee/Jones Family. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Isaac Chamblee Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Isaac Chamblee Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Clark Family. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Robert Clark, Sr., Family. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Samuel Clark Family. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cockrell Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cockrell Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cockrell Family. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cockrell Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Cockrell Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - John Cockrell, Sr., Family. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - John C. Cockrell Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - John C. Cockrell Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Ann Winstead Cockrell Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Nancy Ann Winstead Cockrell Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Daniel Family. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Davidson Family. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Davis Family. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - James Davis, Sr., (d. 1829) Family. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - James Davis, Sr., (d. 1829)/McAfee Family. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - James Davis (1759-1859) Family. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - James Davis (1809-1882) Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - John Davis (1809-1882) Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mary Pearl Davis Family. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - T. T. Davis Confederate Service Record. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dodson Family., folder 1 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dodson Family., folder 2 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dodson Family., folder 3 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dodson Family., folder 4 of 4 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Dodson Family. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Charles Dodson Family. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Joel Dodson and John Nicholas Smith (Schmidt) Descendants. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Joshua Dodson Family. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Parthenia Dodson Family. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Thomas Dodson, Sr., Family. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dooley Family. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Durham Family. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Eatman Family. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Yeatman Family. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Irvin Eatman Family. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - John Eatman (ca. 1691) Family. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - John Eatman (1749-1829) Family. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Eatman Family. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Edmunds Family. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Ezell Family. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gandy Family. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Henry H. Garvin Family. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Henry H. Garvin Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Henry H. Garvin Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Gilbert Family. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - John Hale Gilbert Family. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Joseph Gilbert Family. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Josiah Gilbert Family. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Stephen Gilbert Family. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Goodson Family. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Goodson Family. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Goodson Family. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - John Alexander Goodson, Sr., Family. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Nancy Goodson Family. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sarah Goodson Family. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - William Newton Goodson Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - William Newton Goodson Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - William Newton Goodson Family., folder 3 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Gordon/Arnold/King Family. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Green Family. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hamlin Family. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - William Handeforte Family. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Hansford Family. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - John Hansford, Sr., Family. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - John Hansford, Jr., Family. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hardin Family. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - John Hardin Family. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Horton Family. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Horton Family. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Horton Family. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Horton Family. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Horton Family--video interview of Mary Jo King by Harold Horton and Myra H. Warren, 19 October 1997. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Amos Horton, Jr., Family., folder 1 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Amos Horton, Jr., Family., folder 2 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Amos Horton, Jr., Family., folder 3 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Amos Horton, Jr., Family., folder 4 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Daniel Horton Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Daniel Horton Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Daniel Horton Family. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Jesse Horton Family., folder 1 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Jesse Horton Family., folder 2 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Jesse Horton Family., folder 3 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Jesse Horton Family., folder 4 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - William Horton, Sr., Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - William Horton, Sr., Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hummel Family. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Peter Hummel Family. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Jordan Family. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - King Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - King Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - King Family (photographs)., folder 3 of 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - King Family. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - King Family. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - King Family. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - King[?] Family Photograph. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - King Family. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - King Family. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - King Family (Greene County, Alabama). (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - King Family (North Carolina). (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - King Family (South Carolina). (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - King Family (Tennessee). (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - King/Rudy Family. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - King/Smith Family. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - King/Stamps Family. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Arthur King Family. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Berry Simpson King Family. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Clarence E. King. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - John Berry King. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Joseph Hale King. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Joseph L. King. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Littleberry King Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Littleberry King Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Littleberry King Family., folder 3 of 3 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Richard King (d. 1849) Family. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Richard King, Sr., Family. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Richard King, Jr., (1725-1759) Family. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Sarah Frances King. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Scarborough King. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Susan Edith Smith King Family. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Susan Edith Smith King Family. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - William Rufus King. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Coffman Legg Family. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Locker Family. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Elijah Locker Family. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - James Locker Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - James Locker Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - James Locker Family., folder 3 of 3 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Samuel Locker Family. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - W. R. Locker. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - William Locker Family. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - William Locker Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - William Locker Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - William Locker Family., folder 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mallory Family. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - McAfee Family. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - McAfee Family. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - James McAfee Family. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Thomas McAfee Family. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - William McAfee Family. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - McDaniel Family. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - McDaniel Family. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - McDaniel Family. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Moffett Family. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Andrew Jackson Moore Family. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Leonard Oldham Family. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Patrick Family. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Peebles Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Peebles Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Peebles Family., folder 3 of 3 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Peebles Family. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Mrs. T. E. Roland. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Nicholas Schmidt Family. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Seaward/Soward/Seward Family. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Thomas Seward/Soward, Sr., Family. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Thomas Seward/Soward, Jr., Family. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Thomas Seward/Soward, III, Family. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - William Seward/Soward Family. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Smith Family. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Smith Family. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Smith Family (court records). (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Smith Family. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Smith Family. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Smith/Tallent Family. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Benjamin C. Smith Service Record. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Benjamin Holly Smith Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Benjamin Holly Smith Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Charlie Frost Smith Family. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Jesse Mack Smith Family. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - John Smith Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - John Smith Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - John Smith Family., folder 3 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Joshua A. Smith Family. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Robert Coleman Smith Family. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Susan Edith Smith (King). (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Thomas J. Smith Service Record. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - William Riley Smith Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - William Riley Smith Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Smoot Family. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - John Thomas Stampe (Stamps). (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Stamps Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Stamps Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Stamps Family. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - James Stamps (1759-1845) Family. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - James Stamps (1779-1862) Family. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - James Stamps (1779-1862) Family. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - John Stamps (ca. 1742-1812) Family. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - John Stamps (b. ca. 1751) Family. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - John Stamps (d. ca. 1822) Will. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Joseph and John J. Stamps Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Joseph and John J. Stamps Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Joshua W. Stamps Family. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Lucinda and Charles Stamps Family. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Martha and Sanford Stamps Family. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Martin and Nathan Stamps Family. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Stamps, Sr., Family., folder 1 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Stamps, Sr., Family., folder 2 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Stamps, Sr., Family. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Stamps, Jr., and Elijah Stamps Family. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Timothy Stamps (ca. 1728-1800) Family. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Timothy Stamps (b. ca. 1770-5) Family. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Timothy Stamps (b. ca. 1787) Family. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - William Stamps (ca. 1741-1772) Family. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - William Stamps (1753-1833) Family. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - William Stamps (ca. 1772-1854) Family. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - William Stamps (b. ca. 1770-80) Family. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - William, Elijah, and James Stamps Family. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Starr Family. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Tallent Family. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Tallent Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Tallent Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Tallent Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Tallent Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Tallent Family. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Tallant Tallent Talent Family History 1991. (Box 20)
  - Our Book Early Tallants, volume I. (Box 20)
  - Our Book Aaron Tallent volume V. (Box 20)
  - Aaron Tallent Family. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Odom Castleberry Talent (b. 1802) Family. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Odom Castleberry Tallent (1856-1895) Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Odom Castleberry Tallent (1856-1895) Family. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Tallent Family. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - William Thomas Tallent Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - William Thomas Tallent Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Taylor Family. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Arthur Taylor Family. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Edward Taylor Family. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - John Taylor (1687-by 1725) Family. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - John Taylor (1708-1794) Family. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Thompson Family. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - A Thompson-Bacon Family History. (Box 22)
  - John Thompson (ca. 1690-1753) Family. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - John Thompson (1716-1791) Family. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - William Thompson Family. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Towry Family. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Waggoner Family. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Walters Family. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - A. J. M. Walters. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - John C. Walters Family. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Peter Walters, Sr., Family. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Robert Walters Family. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - William Walters Family. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - William P. Walters Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - William P. Walters Family. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Weeks Family. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Williams Family. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Weeks Williams Family. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Wheaton Williams Family. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Winstead Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Winstead Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Winstead Family, The Descendants of Joseph and Thomas Winstead of Nash/Edgecombe Counties, N.C. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Winstead Family, The Descendants of Joseph and Thomas Winstead of Nash/Edgecombe Counties, N.C. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Winstead Family. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Winstead Family. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Winstead Family. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Descendants of Samuel Winstead (1701-1774). (Box 24)
  - Samuel Winstead, Jr., Family., folder 1 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Samuel Winstead, Jr., Family., folder 2 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Daniel Winston, I, Family. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Daniel Winston, II, Family. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Richard Winston Family. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Wyatt Family. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Genealogical Notes and Charts, A-H. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Genealogical Notes and Charts, I-P. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Genealogical Notes and Charts, Q-Z. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Edgecombe County, North Carolina, Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln County, North Carolina, Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Charles City County, Virginia, Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Gloucester County, Virginia, Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Isle of Wight County, Virginia, Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - New Kent County, Virginia, Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - (Old) Rappahannock County, Virginia, Genealogy. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook. (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Series II: Genealogical Correspondence., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 25-29)
  Series II: Genealogical Correspondence consists of correspondence to Mary Josephine King discussing the genealogies of the Beachboard, Chamblee, Cockrell, Davis, Dodson, Eatman, Gilbert, Goodson, Horton, King, Locker, McAfee, McDaniel, Peebles, Smith, Stamps, Tallent, Taylor, Walters, Williams, Winstead and related families that settled in Virginia, Alabama, Arkansas, Georgia, Maryland, North Carolina, South Carolina, Tennessee, and Texas. Correspondence also includes personal information on the writer and on King. Primary correspondents include Bob Allen Gray, Susan Edith Smith King, and Myra Hester Warren.
  - Martha Walters Aker Correspondence (Walters Family). (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Liz Amundsen Correspondence (Stamps Family). (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Beryl Bailey Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Wilber W. Bandemer Correspondence (Davis Family). (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - David Barnes Correspondence (Tallent Family). (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Priscilla Beachboard Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Frances Beull Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Vickie Blood Correspondence (Smith-Downing Family). (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Verlan G. Bond Correspondence (Stamps-Walters Family). (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ann Pearl Brantley Correspondence (Taylor Family). (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Gusteen Brown and Ann Matthews Correspondence (Black Family). (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Ida May Brown Correspondence (Davis Family). (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Donna Bryant Correpondence (King Family). (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Carol Buchanan Correspondence (Horton-Sledge Family). (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Flossie D. Bueckner Correspondence (Garvin Family). (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Billie and Hall Burks Correspondence (Dodson-Stamps Family). (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Peggy Byers Correspondence (Smith Family). (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Se Layna Walters Campbell Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Carolyn Cannon Correspondence (Goodson Family). (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Elizabeth Scarborough Cockrell Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Onie R. Cockrell Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Robert Cockrell Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Susan Cockrell Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Thomas Cockrell Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Susan Cockrell Compton Correspondence (Cockrell Family). (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Alma Council Correspondence (Horton Family). (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Oma Smith Crow Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Lora Lee Davis Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Howard A. Deaton Correspondence (King Family). (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Andrea King Dobbs Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Juanita Downes Correspondence (Goodson Family). (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Gladys Doyle Correspondence (Horton Family). (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Azalee Duke Correspondence (Tallent Family). (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Betty Eatman Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Magaline Edwards Correspondence (Harbin Family). (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Julia Eldridge Correspondence (Goodson Family). (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Marge Elliott Correspondence (Beachboard Family). (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Helen Embry Correspondence (Tallent-Locker Family). (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Carolyn Ericson Correspondence (Massey-Cockrell Family). (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Birdie Fields Correspondence (Lovell Family). (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Howard C. Floyd Correspondence (Horton Family). (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Georgia Foster Correspondence (McAfee Family). (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Nancy Foster Correspondence (Goodson Family). (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - John Fox Correspondence. (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Mary Cockrell Gambill Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Robert Garvin Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Cleo Gill Correspondence (Peebles-Clark Family). (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Edith Goodson Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Elaine Goodson Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Bob Allen Gray Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Leland Gray Correspondence (Locker Family). (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Shirley Greer Correspondence (Dodson Family). (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Herb Gills Correspondence. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Della Guise Correspondence (Stamps-Dodson Family). (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Martha A. Gupton Correspondence (Winstead Family). (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Gladys Haas Correspondence (Goodson Family). (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Willadeen Hall Correspondence (Beachboard-Smith Family). (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Betty Harrison Correspondence (Joshua Smith and Caroline Family). (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Electra Lovell Hays Correspondence (Smith-Lovell Family). (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Freda Hays Correspondence (Davis Family). (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Claudia Hill Correspondence (Campbell-Davis-McAfee Family). (Box 26, Folder 17)